Guilt is a heavy burden.
The Quarry is a crime, mystery, thriller film directed by Scott Teems.
A man on the run from his own sins, finds himself in a small
border town in Texas, impersonating a reverend.
The town are quickly drawn to the man's unorthodox sermons, but
so is a police chief who has his suspicions.
The Man, played by Shea Whigham.
Chief Moore, played by Michael Shannon.
Celia, played by Catalina Sandino Moreno.
Valentin, played by Bobby Soto.
David Martin, played by Bruno Bichir.
The Quarry is a 2020 American independent Southern Gothic
mystery-thriller film directed by Scott Teems.
It was written by Teems and Andrew Brotzman, who based their screenplay upon the
1995 novel of the same name by South African author Damon Galgut.
Set in the West Texas borderlands, the film focuses on "The Man," an unnamed fugitive drifter, portrayed by Shea Whigham, who takes on the identity of
David Martin, portrayed by Bruno Bichir, a traveling preacher he murders at a quarry after Martin picks him up off the side of a highway.
The Man finds refuge in a border town's dilapidated church, with a young woman named Celia, portrayed by Catalina Sandino
Moreno, providing him with room and board at the house that Martin was set to reside during his stay in town.
Finding solace with his new persona, the drifter soon finds himself with a growing congregation at the church, drawing suspicion from the
town's prejudiced police chief, John Moore, portrayed by Michael Shannon, who is also having a secret affair with Celia.
It was released on April 17, 2020 in theaters by Lionsgate.
The film explores themes of texas, police chief, reverend.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.